Hello friends, all of you have to click on our once again
and you have to
click on Motor Third Party here and here you have to
type the digit, here the
option of Go Digit General Insurance has come,
you have to click on it, after this you have to
click on Sign in with Digital Seva Connect
and here you are getting the option Motor
Insurance, you have to click on it and
here your policy details and here
select vehicle type has to come on this and you have to take
two wheeler third party
and here you have to type the registration number,
after typing the vehicle number you have to
click on search and here you get the
registration year and plus
registration month and here
you get the vehicle variant and here you get the
fuel type and here you have to
type CT and here
you have to tick on the pin code preview policy details
because the policy has
expired first and after that
click on Get Quote and click on SSS, after this
you have to change 1 lakh to 6000
and after that here is the PA  Cover,
you have to untick on this and after this
click on recalculate and here you
get the name Basu Herem Owner's name and
here you have to type the owner's mobile number
and the owner's email ID
after typing the mobile number you have to come down here you get
your complete details and here you have to click on the complete address
and here friends
if you do not have a PAN card then you have to
click on it and after this you have to
come down and click on save code here it will take
some time and here you have to
click on generate policy so
after coming here you see the Chase number here
plus the engine number is visible and here the
partner reference number means this is the
CSC ID with which you are making it is
visible here and you have to come down
and here you have to make it online in the payment mode
and after this click on generate policy
and after this you are
getting the option of pay here you have to pay
again here you have to
type the password of the CSC ID to make the payment
after this here  We have to
type the six digit PIN of CSC wallet and
then click on pay, then
you can see that our
policy has been successfully done and from
here we will download the policy and
print the first page of it and give it to the customer, so
friends, how did you like the video, do
tell us by commenting, then we will
meet again in a new video, till then
Jai
[Music]
Hind